Hello, I'm Saya Kanazawa from Nogizaka46!
Today, I'm here at Hokkaido Park for the "Manatsu no Zenkoku Tour 2023".
We're here at Hokkaido Park.
Today we're here at Hokkaido Park, where we went undercover last year.
We went undercover in the merchandise store and we were trying to see if we would get caught or not, and we didn't get caught at all.
It's surprisingly easy to go unnoticed.
I have Saya Kanazawa's ribbon holder here, if you don't mind.
I'm fine, thank you.
Thank you very much. Please give me a shock that no one will notice.
Thank you.
Is that possible?
Wait a minute.
I was so frustrated that I asked for one more chance, and they said they'd let me go see you in the merchandise booth again.
I'm going to make sure I'm in perfect condition today so that no one will recognize me.
I'm a little nervous because there are a lot of people who are wondering if you guys are doing it, but I'm going to do my best.
I'm a little nervous, but I'm going to do my best with all my energy.
Thank you very much.
Okay, so I'm done with my disguise.
I was so excited this time.
Before I came here, I was looking at the merchandise counter.
I thought there were a lot of people wearing dumplings.
So I asked them to put on a dango.
And I put on glasses. Big glasses.
I also put on a big mask to disguise myself.
It worked, didn't it?
I just wanted to make sure they wouldn't recognize me.
We have this member here today.
Yes, Kyokushin's Mr. Ikedate.
Thank you very much.
Do you think they'll know?
I think they will.
Not at all. He's wearing a mask to make himself look bigger.
That's right.
I haven't succeeded at all.
My face looks like this.
It's not good.That's not good.
I'll find you in a second.
I really do.
But part of me wants to be found out, and part of me doesn't want to be found out.
That's true.
That's why I want to do my best.
I'm nervous.
I'm looking forward to the results.
Thank you very much.
I'm going undercover.
Have a good trip.
Please cheer for me.
I'm trying to get people to buy this, but it's sold out.
I'd like to say, "How about this?
Okay, let's go.
Let's put on something else, too.
They're in front of us, but they don't know we're here.
Welcome.
Here you go.
This one.
Sayaka.
Is it me?
Yes, it's me.
Is it me? It's coming out.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
But if you don't mind...
I'd have to buy it.
No problem.
I'll take this one then.
Yes, ma'am.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very much.Thank you.
Ha-ha-ha.
Thank you very much.
A little secret, please.
Please don't tell anyone.
Uh-huh.
Not at all.
Um, I've been catching rings since the first shot.
Wow!
I didn't think it was that fast.
But wait, it's so frustrating, so frustrating!
But I was happy because it's me, and...
I was so happy that you also bought this Masker key ring!
Thank you very much!
Next, I'm going to untie my glasses and hair and get out of here.
I'm going to change my clothes with the mask on.
I'm always riding too much, and I think they'll recognize me.
But you know what I mean.
I'm just going to have fun with you guys and do my best.
I'm here to be exposed.
They're looking at me like crazy.
They're staring at me. They're staring at me.
Welcome!
So, the Gamber Band...
Here you go.
Mr. Kanagawa, isn't it?
Mr. Kanagawa.
I'm so happy to see you.
Thank you, Sakura Endo.
May I have one from Ms. Kanagawa, too?
May I?
Here they are.
Thank you very much.
That's right.
You didn't notice that the first time?
I was a little confused at first.I was a little confused at first.
Really?
Yes, I'm sure. That's great. Thank you.
Sorry for the wait.
Saya Kanagawa.
Saya from Kanagawa.
Thank you very much.
I'm so obvious. Today, why?
That's why.
I was able to serve one person.
It's so obvious.
It wasn't that obvious.
Surprisingly, the first one...
Did you notice? I said...
No, I didn't notice at all.
I'm glad you noticed me in the middle.
Now, I'd like to continue with the mask off.
Let's go!
Okay, here we go!
All right, everybody, look at me.
Look at me.
Okay, I'm already unmasked.
Pan.
Nice to meet you.
Please come in.
Welcome.
How's it going?
Do you recommend it?
Do you recommend it? I recommend this one by Saya Kanagawa.
I also have this one.
I'll buy them.
Thank you very much.
I'll treasure them.Treasure it.
Treasure it?
I'll treasure it.
Yes! Thank you very much.
Thank you very much for this canna.
Did you buy it?
That's it!
Sorry, I'm a different member,
I'm sorry, you're a different member, but I'd like a Europa Linka and a Pomis Miphone keychain.
Yes, well, well, okay.
Have fun at the show!
And the radio run afterwards.
Oh, yes, there will be a rad run!
Please listen to it!
Over here, thank you very much!
Congratulations, Sambo.
Thank you very much.
Yes, sorry, we'll see you at the show.
OK.
Thank you. Bye-bye.
Thank you.
Cute, thank you.
Have fun.
Thank you. Thank you.
Yes, all exposed!
All nicely exposed!
So, the infiltration of the goods is over.
As a result, all of us were exposed.
But I was so happy that I was exposed more than last year.
I'm already at zero or a hundred, right now....
But it was a lot of fun.
I think we were able to make people a little more excited before the concert.
No matter what kind of disguise you wear, Saya Kanagawa will always be recognized.
I'm going to do my best at the live after this!I have a live concert later on, so I'll do my best.
Please subscribe to my channel and give me a high rating!
This is Saya Kanagawa! Thank you for your hard work!
Thanks everyone!